To walk the path of a hero, you have to see how it all began.
Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk is a drama, war film directed by Ang Lee.
19-year-old Billy Lynn is brought home for a victory
tour after a harrowing Iraq battle.
Through flashbacks the film shows what really happened to his squad –
contrasting the realities of war with America's perceptions.
Billy Lynn, played by Joe Alwyn.
David Dime, played by Garrett Hedlund.
Marcellino 'Mango' Montoya, played by Arturo Castro.
Foo, played by Mason Lee.
Lodis, played by Stro.
Crack, played by Beau Knapp.
Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk is a 2016 war drama film directed by Ang Lee and written by
Jean-Christophe Castelli, based on the 2012 novel of the same name by Ben Fountain.
The film stars Joe Alwyn, Garrett Hedlund, Kristen Stewart,
Vin Diesel, Steve Martin, and Chris Tucker.
Principal photography began in April 2015 in Georgia.
The film is a co-production between the United
States, the United Kingdom, and China.
The film had its world premiere at the 54th New York Film Festival on October 14, 2016, and was
theatrically released in North America on November 11, 2016, by TriStar Pictures.
It had high production costs associated with being the first-ever feature film using an extra-high frame
rate of 120 frames per second, further complicated by the 3D format, at 4K UHD resolution.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and it grossed $31
million worldwide against its $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of post-traumatic stress disorder (ptsd), based on
novel or book, war veteran, american football, thanksgiving.
The tone is emotional.